翻译校对       Mam
日  听      大海
日听校对       Syura
翻译        葉隠
时间轴       卡卡
压制      娜夏
OP&ED       葉隠
Syura
诸神字幕组
遅れていくとうるさいからな
They're going to hound me if I'm late.
"Music Room #3"
Where...
...is this?
- Welcome!
いらっしゃいませ
扉を開けると そこは南国でした
When I opened the door,
there were the south tropics.
Mother, up in Heaven, this is the club
I was forced to join last week,
天国のお母さん これが先週入部させられた桜蘭ホスト部です
the Ouran Host Club.
"The Job of a High School Host!"
Oh, it's you, Haruhi. You're late.
何だ ハルヒか 遅いぞ
According to my calendar,
this is definitely still early April.
暦によると 確か今は四月上旬かと
Huddling under a kotatsu table,
fearing the cold would be nonsense!
冷気を恐れ コタツに縮こまるなど庶民の感覚（ナンセンス）
Why else do we have this perfect
heating and cooling system?
この完璧な空調設備は何のためだ
Do you have some sort of criticism
of our club's policies?
何か我が部の方針に批判でもあるのかな
Haruhi- kun, you owe us
a debt of 8 million yen.
八百万円の借金を背負うハルヒ君
"Eight million yen"
Fine men do not bundle up
in bulky clothing.
いい男は着膨れなどしない
It may be a chilling early spring out
in the world, but in our club,
世間が肌寒い春先だろうと
この部では 凍える子ネコたちを暖かな南国オーラで迎え入れる
we welcome our chilly little kittens
to a warm, south tropical aura!
Yes! Today, this place
is a supreme paradise,
そう 今日ここは至上の楽園 常夏の暑い暑いアイランドなのだ
a hot, hot island
of everlasting summer!
むしろあらゆる意味で寒いのですが
I, on the other hand, feel a chill,
in every sense of the word.
この私立桜蘭学院は 一に家柄 二にお金
Those with the wherewithal,
first in social standing,
and second in money- spend their time here,
at the private Ouran Academy.
財あるものは暇を持つ
As such, Ouran Host Club
is where handsome boys
かくして桜蘭ホスト部とは
暇を持て余す美少年たちが
with too much time on their hands
entertain the girls,
同じく暇な女生徒たちを持て成す
who also have too much
time on their hands.
It is the school's own personal,
elegant playground for the super-rich.
スーパー金持ち学校独自の 華麗なる遊戯なのである
"The Host Club is now open for business"
何と言う無情
What heartlessness!
Even with my lustrous skin, like ivory,
この象牙のような艶やかな肌も
and my outfit, like that of a Balinese king,
all too fitting for me,
似合いすぎるバリの王のごとき装束も
I am no more than a slave
before my goddess,
女神の前では跪き 忠誠を誓うただの下僕
kneeling, and swearing my loyalty.
環君
Tamaki- kun...
Tamaki-sama...
環様
Fantastic!
素敵
Oh yes, next week, Ouran Host Club
will be sponsoring a dance party.
そうそう 来週は我が桜蘭ホスト部主催の
ダンスパーティーを開催するからね
ダンスパーティー？
A dance party?
What will you be doing
at this dance party?
ダンスパーティーってどんなことするの
We're renting the large hall
in the central building...
中央棟の大広間を貸しきりで
"Hikaru Hitachiin, High School 1st-Year"
最高に盛り上げるからね
...and throwing a big main event there.
"Kaoru Hitachiin, High School 1st-Year"
Although, I really wanted to spend
the time alone with you, Kaoru.
本当は 二人で過ごしたかったけどな 馨
Don't say that, Hikaru.
I'm the one who really wanted it...
言わないでよ 光 本当は僕だって…
Fantastic!
素敵 兄弟愛南国風味よ
Brotherly love, with a south
tropical flavor!
The guests seem even more
worked-up than usual, huh?
何かいつもよりお客さんのテンションが高いですね
A little moderate exposure is popular.
程よい露出は受けがいい
Did you come up with this
tropical project, Kyoya-senpai?
このトロピカル企画は鏡夜先輩が
I have no decision-making authority.
俺に決定権はないよ
This club's policies are all
laid out by the king, Tamaki.
この部の方針はすべてキングの環が仕切ってる
Although, I may have
found it worth the effort
ま さりげなくあいつのデスクにバリの写真集を置いた甲斐はあったかな
to casually slip a photo book
of Bali onto his desk.
This guy is the shadow king.
陰のキングだ この人は
Ta-da!!
ハニー君 かわいい
Honey- kun, you're so cute!
Hee hee, these are Balinese flowers.
We had them flown in.
これバリのお花 空輸したの
あっ 崇
Ah, Takashi!
Look! Now we match!
ね～お揃い
"Takashi Morinozuka ('Mori' for short)
High School 3rd-Year"
"Mitsukuni Haninozuka ('Honey' for short)
You're all in camellias!
椿院の君
As usual, I'm not sure what
what those two are doing means.
相変わらず意味不明だな あの二人も
Haruhi- kun...
ハルヒ君
Haruhi- kun, aren't you going to
wear a south tropical outfit?
ハルヒ君は南国衣装着ないの
I'd sure like to see that.
見たいな
No, I...
いいえ 自分は…
I just think that it's natural to wear
an early-spring outfit during early spring.
やっぱり春先は春先らしい格好するのが自然と思いますし
Haruhi, we have one ready for you.
What's more, it's paired with mine.
ハルヒの分も用意したぞ しかも俺とペアだ
No thank you.
結構です
Haruhi- kun, you have a strong
sense of the seasons, huh?
ハルヒ君は季節感を大切にしてるのね
Then I hope that the cherry blossoms
are in full bloom for the dance party.
だったら ダンスパーティーの時には
桜が満開に咲いてるといいわよね
The two of us, dancing among
the fluttering cherry blossoms...
舞い散る桜の中で踊る二人 夢よね
It's so dreamy...
You really think so?
そういうものですか
Ladies, you're so cute
to have such dreams.
"Haruhi Fujioka, High School 1st-Year"
みなさん 夢があって かわいいですね
"The Host Club's promising natural rookie"
失礼 そろそろ指名交替の時間だと思うのだけれど
Excuse me...
I believe that it's just about time
for designee changes.
Oh, I'm sorry. You must be
my next appointment, Miss...
すみません 次にご予約の…
Kasugazaki Kanako, 2nd-Year Class B.
二年B組 春日崎奏子よ
You're even cuter than the rumors.
噂以上にかわいいのね
決めたわ 次はあなたをお気に入りにして差し上げてよ
I've made up my mind.
I'm going to make you my new favorite.
I can't accept this.
"Ramen"
納得いかん
Sir, stop eating that commoner's ramen,
殿 庶民ラーメン食べてないで
and come help us with
the dance party planning.
ダンスパーティーのプランニング手伝ってよ
Is Princess Kasuga
taking a liking to Haruhi
ハルヒが春日姫に気に入られたのがそんなに気に食わんのかね
really bothering you that much?
Her illness isn't something
that just started, right?
彼女の病気は今に始まったことじゃないだろう
Illness?
病気？
Wandering host-hopping disease.
流離のホスト巡り病
Otherwise known as
never-the-same-boy-twice disease.
つまり 男とっかえひっかえ病ね
Usually, our regular customers
designate the same host in perpetuity,
普通常連客は決めた相手を永久指名するものなんだが
彼女は定期的にお気に入りを替える傾向があってね
but she tends to change
her favorite on a regular basis.
Up until last time,
she was with Tama-chan, right?
この前までは タマちゃんだったんだよね
"The pair in days gone by (one week ago)"
あ～ 自分のお客を取られたから
Ah, this is because he had
his guest taken from him.
"Understands now"
It is not! That's not why!
違ーう そんなことじゃない
もう我慢の限界だ ハルヒ ちゃんと女の格好をしろ
I'm at the limits of my patience!
Haruhi, start dressing like a girl!
Why do you have to be so
woefully popular with the girls,
女でありながら何が悲しくて女にモテモテにならねばいかんのだ
when you yourself are a girl!?
To put it bluntly, the only ones who know
that you're a girl are in this club!
はっきり言って お前が女と知ってるのは部員だけだぞ
She's opted out of taking
any gym classes.
体育は選択制で 取ってないし
Attendance numbers are mixed between
boys and girls, so no one can tell.
出席番号も男女混合なのでバレてないし
"King's private property"
Daddy... Daddy...
お父さんは お父さんはな～
...wants to see you the way
you were back then!
この頃のお前が見たいんだよ
Please don't go blowing up
my photos without asking me!
人の写真を勝手に引き伸ばさないでください
The more I look at this,
the more I marvel at it.
見れば見るほど不思議だよね
How is it that this can become that?
何でこれがあれになっちゃうわけ
"This" "That"
The day before the entrance ceremonies,
入学前日 近所の子に髪の毛にガムをくっ付けられて
I had some gum stuck in my hair from
one of the children in the neighborhood.
It was such a pain to get out
that I cut it off.
面倒だから 切っちゃったんです
''Ore''[ore-l] didn't really care if
I looked like a boy.
俺としては 男に見られても 別にどうでもいいし
Girls should not be referring
to themselves as "ore"!
女の子が「俺」なんていけません
お母さん ハルヒが汚い言葉使うよ～
Mommy! Haruhi is using dirty words!
Who's "Mommy"?
お母さんって
From a club position standpoint,
I guess I am.
ポジション的に 俺かな
Well after all, I can pay back
more of my debt before I graduate
だって 卒業まで雑用係よりは
by being a designated host,
than I can as an errand boy.
ホストになって指名取るほうが借金返せそうだし
By the way, do you have any
experience in social dancing?
ところで お前 社交ダンスの経験は…
It's essential for the party.
パーティーじゃ必須だぞ
Huh? No, but the party has nothing
to do with my quota, right?
いや でも パーティーはノルマに関係ないでしょう
I'm not all that interested in going
to events, so if I could be excused...
イベントとかには興味ないし できれば欠席…
No, social dances are a common
practice for a gentleman.
いや 社交ダンスは紳士の常識
If you want to walk the path
of the host that badly,
そこまでホストの道を歩みたいなら
その覚悟の程を見せてもらおう ハルヒ君
then you have to show us how far
you're willing to go, Haruhi- kun.
If you cannot master
the waltz in one week,
一週間で見事ワルツをマスターし
and demonstrate it to us
at next week's party,
来週のパーティーで披露できなければ
then I will expose the fact
that you are a girl,
女の子であることを暴露して 雑用係に格下げだ
and bust you back down
to errand boy!
"Debtor student"
"The next day"
Quick, quick, slow...
クイック クイック スロー クイック クイック スロー
Good, Haruhi- kun. On "slow,"
bring your feet together.
よくって ハルヒ君 スローで足を揃えるの
The gentleman always leads.
必ず殿方からリード パートナーの女性を良く見て
Be sure to look at the girl
you're dancing with.
Right.
I'm so sorry, Kasugazaki- san!
すみません 春日崎さん
That's all right, Haruhi- kun.
いいのよ ハルヒ君
You're looking gloomy, sir.
たそがれてんな 殿
He said that he wanted to be
the one she practiced with.
自分が練習相手になりたかったんだって
He's too tall to stand in
as a woman for Haruhi- kun.
身長的にハルヒの女役なんて無理なのにね
すいません 春日崎さん 練習相手なんて…
Thank you so much, Kasugazaki- san,
for letting me practice with you.
Oh, that's okay.
あら いいのよ 聞けば特訓の為暫く接客は控えるそうじゃない
I hear you're refraining from
entertaining any customers,
so you can get in some
special training, aren't you?
I'm that much happier
to have you all to myself.
かえって独占できて嬉しいわ
Yeah...
あら カップ新しくしたの 地海苔ね
Oh, my! You got new cups?
Ginori, right?
Jinori? [land-grown seaweed]
地海苔？
You do indeed have a keen eye.
They arrived only yesterday.
さすがお目が高い 昨日入荷したばかりの品です
Lately, our club has been seeking
to improve its tea sets.
最近我が部は ティーセットの向上に力を入れてましてね
I see. It's a nice color.
Very lovely.
そう いい色ね 素敵だわ
食器がお好きなんですね
You must really like tableware, huh?
べ べ べ べ 別に好きじゃないわよ やあね 何言ってんの
N-n-not really, no, I don't.
My word, what are you talking about?
好きなんだ
She does like it.
But why would she hide it?
でも 何で隠すんだろう
Hello, I've brought
the teacups you ordered.
こんにちは 注文のティーカップをお持ちしました
Ah, thank you.
あー ご苦労様
Every item that you choose for us
is popular with the girls.
君に選んでもらった品はどれも女の子たちに評判がいい
It's very impressive.
さすがだね
That's good to hear.
それは良かった
業者の方ですか？
Are you a dealer?
一般の生徒だよ 制服着てるでしょう
I'm just a regular student.
I'm wearing a uniform, see?
Haruhi- kun, you're so funny.
ハルヒ君ったら おもしろい
Still, I can't blame you.
でも無理ないわ
He doesn't look like the heir
to a first-class corporation, after all.
とても一流企業の御曹子には見えないものね
Heir?
御曹子？
His family business, Suzushima Trading,
彼の家 珠洲島通商は食器輸入を旗艦業務にする会社で
is a company whose business centers
around the importing of tablewares.
Currently, it has the top
market share in the country.
今のところ そのシェアは我が国トップだ
Oh, yeah?
So whenever anything exceptional comes in,
we've asked him to send it our way.
だから逸品が入ったらうちに入れてくれるように頼んだんだ
That's because we trust your eye
for these things, Suzushima- kun.
君の目は信頼できるからね 珠洲島君
Oh, no, my eye still has a long way to go.
いや 僕の目なんて まだまだです
Your studying abroad in England
starts next month, was it?
イギリス留学は来月からだっけ
Yes. Well, I'll be off.
ええ それじゃ僕は…
ホスト部は楽しいですかな？
Are you enjoying the Host Club?
Are you close to that man
who was just here?
今の人と親しいんですか
Huh!? N-n-not really, no, I'm not!
べ べ べ 別に親しくないわよ やあね 何聞くの ハルヒ君
M-my word, what are you
talking about, Haruhi- kun?
N-now, if you'll excuse me...
Take care.
きょう きょうは失礼するわ ご機嫌よう
Haru-chan!
ハールちゃん あのね 珠洲島君は春日ちゃんの許婚なんだよ
You know what? Suzushima- kun
is Kasuga-chan's fiancé.
Kyoya, how long have you known?
鏡夜 お前いつから知ってた
About him being her fiancé?
許婚の件か
I do, of course, conduct general
research on our customers.
もちろん お客様のことは一通りリサーチしてある
The two are childhood friends.
二人は幼馴染 婚約は両親の決め事のようだ
Their engagement appears to have been
arranged by their parents.
It didn't particularly seem to
be information that we could use,
特に利用価値のない情報だから 放っておいたが
so I just left it alone.
お前な…
Why, you...
Suzushima Toru: Outstanding grades,
fair social status,
珠洲島享 成績優秀 家柄まあまあ 容姿人並み
ordinary looks, with reliability
as a strong point.
真面目さが取柄で 難をあげるなら
If I had to fault him for anything...
Not much presence.
影が薄い
He's faint-hearted.
気が弱い
In other words, he's plain. That's it.
つまり 地味だ 以上
They're all but merciless
toward other boys.
男に対してはまるで容赦ないな
Toru- kun is a good boy. Right?
享君はいい子だよ ねっ
Yeah.
それでは 対策を検討する
All right, then...
Let's examine our strategy.
Which one?
何の？
Ouran Host Club
我が桜蘭ホスト部は女の子を幸せにするために存在するのだ
exists in order to bring happiness
to the girls!
My little lambs,
who have gathered here tonight,
"One week later"
今宵集まりし子羊たちよ 桜蘭ホスト部ダンスパーティーへ
Ouran Host Club bids
you a fond welcome...
...to this dance party.
ようこそ
We invite you to enjoy yourselves
to your heart's content,
本日は存分に我がホスト部一同との
as you dance with the Host Club members.
ダンスを楽しんで頂きたく思います
In addition, the guest who is
recognized as the best dancer,
なお 最高のダンスと認められ 今夜のクイーンに選ばれたお客様には
and is chosen as tonight's queen
will receive an impassioned kiss
on the cheek from the king.
キングより その頬に熱いキスが送られます
Good luck to you,
頑張ってね ベイビー
baby.
Haruhi, your enthusiasm is low.
ハルヒ テンション低いぞ
I'm not used to this sort of thing.
こういうのは慣れてないの ダンスパーティーなんて
The only dance party I've ever been to
is the bon-odori festival
at the neighborhood park.
近所の公園に盆踊りに行ったぐらいで
You probably can't call
that a dance party.
それは多分ダンスパーティーとはいわないが
Well, you're here anyway,
ま せっかくだから料理くらい食べておいたらどうだ ご馳走だぞ
so why don't you at least
try the cuisine?
There's a real spread.
A spread?
ご馳走
L-like with fancy tuna?
お 大トロとか
Fan-
オ・オ・トロ
- cy
tuna!?
大至急 ここに大トロを
- Get some fancy tuna here, stat!
- You poor thing... Oh, you poor thing...
可哀相に…
- Add some deluxe sushi.
- You poor thing... Oh, you poor thing...
特上寿司 追加だ
Damn these rich people...
くそ 金持ちどもめ
Um...
あのう…
Haruhi- kun...
ハルヒ君
I've been looking for you.
You'll dance with me, won't you?
探してたのよ 一緒に踊ってくれるでしょう
Yes, of course.
ええ もちろん
春日ちゃん来たよ
Kasuga-chan is here.
Well then...
では 作戦開始ということで
...that means that
the mission is underway.
Roger!
了解
何 誘拐？
What's this? A kidnapping?
They're here!
来た来た
You didn't have to be so high-handed.
何もこんな強引に
Never mind, just get changed.
いいから さっさと着替える
Having an "accident" happen right
at the end would be more thrilling.
ラストにはアクシデントがあったほうが盛り上がる
Remember, Haruhi, your time limit
is 20 minutes to the party climax.
いいか ハルヒ
リミットはパーティークライマックスまでの二十分
すでに向かいの教室に珠洲島氏を呼び出してある
We've already called Suzushima
to the adjoining classroom.
Gracefully ask him what his feelings are.
うまく気持ちを聞きだしてね
Although, since this is
his highness's strategy,
まっ 殿の作戦だから いまいち不安だけどね
there's something unsettling about it.
Hey! What's the big idea,
having everyone in here?
こら 全員こっちに来てどうする お客様の相手…
Who's looking after our guests-
What do you think, sir?
どうよ 殿
Haru-chan, you look cute!
ハルちゃん かわいい
My face feels heavy, and it's hard
to walk in these shoes.
づらが重い 靴が歩きづらい
Good luck in there!
頑張ってこいよ
かかか かわいすぎる
S-s-she's just too cute...
君がこの手紙を ずいぶんイメージと違うな
You wrote this letter?
You're a lot different
from what I imagined.
手紙？
Letter?
I'm in love-love!
ラブラブゥゥ
"Love-love"
From the first time I ever saw you,
あなたを一目見た時から 私の心は超ラブラブ てへ
my heart fell in super love-love! Tee-hee!
It's like, I'm in a never-ending
tropical cyclone, not unlike a typhoon,
宛も永遠に熱帯性低気圧に変わらない台風の如く
where love is whipping around in my heart,
私の心にはラブが吹き荒れているのであります
and I want to have a rendezvous
with you on Noah's Ark! I do, I do!"
あなたと一緒にノアの方舟でランデブーしたいのだ のだ のだ
Who wrote this letter?
誰だ こんな手紙書いたの
"Collaborative piece"
Huh? Have we met somewhere?
あれ 君 どっかで
No! We've never spoken before!
いいえ お話しするのは初めてです
"Yikes!"
I'm sorry.
ごめんね
I appreciate what you've said,
but I cannot respond to your letter.
せっかくだけど この手紙には応えられない
I already have another girl
who is dear to me.
僕には大事に思ってる子がいるから
Suzushima- san, is she your...
その人は珠洲島さんの…
Unfortunately,
she isn't my girlfriend.
残念ながら 恋人じゃない
Or I should say,
she's through with me.
というか 愛想をつかされてる
彼女には 華やかで自信に溢れた男が似合ってる
She'd be better suited having a more
dazzling, self-confident man.
一体どこへ連れていってくださるのかしら
Just where exactly is it
that you're taking me?
You...
君には 多分君には 駆け引きとか向いてないんだと思う
You probably aren't the sort of person
who is cut out for manipulating others.
I'm not sure what you mean.
どういう意味かしら
No matter how many hosts
you hop around to,
彼の気を引くために いくら流離のホスト巡りをしてみても
in order to gain his attention,
you always seem happier
when you look at the teacups.
君はティーカップを見ているほうが よほど幸せそうだ
見てご覧 奏子
Look at these, Kanako.
How pretty!
綺麗
A Wedgwood... a Foley...
a Worcester...
ウェッジウッド フォリー ウースター
Over here is a Ginori, and a Meissen.
こっちのが地海苔 マイセン
Kanako, you're going to be my wife,
奏子は僕のお嫁さだから 全部教えてあげる ね
so I'll tell you about
all of them, okay?
Mm-hmm!
It doesn't matter.
もう いいのよ
No matter what I do,
he doesn't notice me in the least.
私が何をしても あの人ちっとも気にしないし
留学だって 私の知らないうちに決めちゃって
He even decided to study abroad
without me knowing it.
That's why I'd like to change, as well.
Looking at the world,
だから 僕も変わりたいと思ってる
世界を見て もっと大きな男になりたいんだ
I want to become an even greater man.
I know it's selfish of me,
but what if you were to wait for me?
勝手だけど 待っていてもらえたらと…
That really is selfish of you, huh?
それは本当に勝手ですね
It's crazy to think she'd understand you,
unless you tell her so.
伝えもしないで 分ってもらおうなんて無茶な話です
You have clear feelings for her,
so where is the need to put it off?
はっきりした思いがあるのに 先延ばしにする必要がどこに…
I think that people can begin to change
変わりたいと思ったときから 人は変われるんだと思います
from the moment they decide they want to.
Kanako...
奏子
Oh, I'm sorry. I seem to be
interrupting something.
あら ごめんなさい 何かお邪魔しちゃったみたいね あたし…
I'll just...
Kanako!
奏子 奏子
Kanako!!
Didn't we just complicate things?
逆に拗れてません
彼は追い掛けて走り出した
He did go running after her.
Ouran Host Club...
我が桜蘭ホスト部は 女の子の幸せのために存在する か
... exists in order to bring
happiness to girls, huh?
And now, ladies and gentlemen,
それでは 皆様
this enjoyable evening of ours
has at last come to its final song.
楽しい今宵の一時も いよいよ最後の一曲となりました
The Host Club's last waltz
falls upon this couple.
我々ホスト部からのラストワルツはこのお二人に…
Princess Kasuga,
春日姫 僕と踊っていただけますか
may I have this dance?
Yes.
I love you.
君が好きだ ずっと好きだった
I've always loved you.
I'm proposing to you once again.
改めてプロポーズする
Tonight, my hopping around
to different hosts is over.
今夜で 流離のホスト巡りはおしまいね
May this awkward couple be blessed!
不器用カップルに祝福あれ
Tonight's dance queen...
本日のダンスクイーンは…
春日崎奏子姫に決定しました
...is hereby declared to be
Princess Kasugazaki Kanako.
それでは 祝福のキスをキングより…
Now then, the blessed kiss
from the king...
I'm on.
出番か
...has been switched
to Fujioka Haruhi!
を変更して 藤岡ハルヒから…
Hey!
After all, Kyoya-senpai said
that having an "accident"
だって ラストにはアクシデントが…
happen right at the end
would be more thrilling.
あったほうが盛り上がるって鏡夜先輩が
It's just on the cheek, right?
Go ahead and accept it,
どうせほっぺだろう 受けてきなよ
to commemorate your graduation
from host-hopping.
流離のホスト巡り卒業の記念だ
そりゃいくらなんでも…
Of all the things to put me through...
We'll cut your debt by one-third.
借金三分の一カット
Well, as long as it's just
a peck on the cheek...
まあ ほっぺぐらいなら
Say, by any chance, could this
be Haru-chan's first kiss?
ねね もしかしてハルちゃん ファーストキスなんじゃ…
What!?
そのキス 待ったあ
Hold that kiss!
つい成り行きでファーストキスを女の子に捧げてしまったけれど
The course of events played out such
that my first kiss went to a girl,
なんか気分のいい夜なんで
but it was such a pleasant evening...
これでよしとするか
... so I guess that's good
enough for me.
女の子だってバレると さすがにホスト部にはいられませんね
If word gets out that I'm a girl,
"Physical exams"
I couldn't very well stay
in the Host Club.
心配するな ハルヒ お前の秘密は必ず俺が守ってやる
"Naked"
Don't you worry, Haruhi.
Whatever happens,
I will protect your secret!
Next time, "Beware the Physical Exam"
桜蘭高校ホストクラブ 来週も
Ouran High School Host Club
will be waiting for you, next week!
お待ちしております